I have seen APC today. He is a very pleasant gentleman who is 42 years old, 344 pounds.
He is 59. He has BMA of 51. He has been overweight for 10 years since the age of 33. At his highest,
he was 358 pounds. At his lowest, 260. He is pursuing surgical attempts of weight loss
to feel good, get healthy and begin to exercise again. He wants to be able to exercise and
play volleyball. Physically, he is sluggish. He gets tired quickly. He doesn't go out often.
he gets tired quickly
When he loses weight, he always regains it and he gains back more than he lost. His biggest
weight loss is 25 pounds and it was 3 months before he gained it back. He did 6 months of
not drinking alcohol and not taking in many calories. He has been on multiple commercial
weight loss programs including Slim Fast for 1 month, 1 year ago and Atkins Diet for 1 month,
and atkins died for one month two years ago
2 years ago. Past medical history. He has difficulty climbing stairs, difficulty with
airline seats, tying shoes used to public seating, difficulty walking, high cholesterol and high
blood pressure. He has asthma and difficulty walking, 2 blocks are going 8 to 10 steps. He
has sleep apnea and snoring. He is diabetic on medication. He has joint pain, knee pain, back pain, foot and ankle pain, leg and foot swelling.